https://www.orage.com/ca_en/privacy-policy

ORAGE
Skip to content
SPOIL SOMEONE AND WE WILL SPOIL YOU!
For a limited time, get a gift card back with every eligible purchase: CLICK HERE FOR MORE DETAILS
Privacy Policy
OUR COMMITMENT TO PRIVACY
Protecting Your Privacy Is Important To Us And We Recognize That Your Personal Information Must Be Used Responsibly. Our Privacy Policy ("Privacy Policy") Informs You Of The Information That Orage, Mtndewds Distribution Inc. And Its Affiliates ("Mtndewds") Gathers In Relation To The Operation Of Its Website, How The Information Is Used And How You Can Access And Modify Collected Information.Please Note That This Privacy Policy Applies Only To Information Collected From You By Mtndewds Via Our Website. This Privacy Policy Does Not Apply To Third Party Websites, And Mtndewds Is Not Responsible For The Content Of Such Third Party Websites Or The Privacy Practices Of Such Third Parties.
WHAT AND WHY INFORMATION IS COLLECTED?
You Can Access Some Areas Of Our Website Without Submitting Any Personal Information. Mtndewds Collects Personal Information Only If You Choose To Complete The Online Forms To Contact Us, Complete A Profile, Participate In A Contest, Provide Feedback Or Request Information. The Personal Information That Mtndewds Collects Through These Sections Of Our Website Includes Your Name, Username, Password, Email Address, Postal Address, Phone Number, Credit Card Number And Any Other Personal Information That You Choose To Include In Your Profile. Mtndewds May Also Collect Certain Non Personal Information In Relation To The Operation Of Our Website, Including Ip Addresses, Browser Or Operating System Information, Data On Advertisements Or Links On Which You Click, And The Websites That You Visit Before Or After You Visit Our Website. We Do Not Sell Or Share Personal Information To Any Third Party Outside Mtndewds. The Purpose Of The Collected Information Is To Track Your Visit On Our Website. This Information Helps Us To Improve Our Website, Respond To Your Requests And Customize Your Shopping Experience.
PROTECTION OF CHILDREN'S PERSONAL INFORMATION
Mtndewds Is Concerned About Protecting The Safety And Privacy Of Children. We Do Not Knowingly Or Specifically Request Or Collect Personal Information From Or About Children And Do Not Market Specifically To Children. We Do, However, Sell Children's Products For Purchase By Adults.
DISCLOSURE & PROTECTION OF YOUR INFORMATION
Mtndewds May Disclose Your Personal Information To Third Party Partners Hired To Provide Services On Our Behalf, Including Support Services, Website Services, Delivering Materials, Answering Customer Questions. Mtndewds Will Only Provide Those Third Party Partners With The Personal Information They Need To Deliver The Services To Us And/or On Our Behalf.To Prevent Unauthorized Access Or Disclosure, Maintain Data Accuracy And Facilitate The Appropriate Use Of Information, Mtndewds Uses Physical, Technological And Administrative Procedures To Attempt To Protect The Integrity Of Its Site And The Confidentiality Of The Data Collected Through The Website. Nevertheless, Internet Transmissions Are Never Completely Private Or Secure. Mtndewds Cannot Be Liable For Any Breaches Of Confidentiality Due To System Failures Or Unauthorized Access By Third Parties.
YOUR ACCEPTANCE OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY
The Use Of This Website Constitutes The User's Acceptance Of This Privacy Policy. If You Do Not Agree To This Privacy Policy, You May Not Use The Website. Mtndewds Reserves The Right, In Our Discretion, To Change, Modify, Add Or Remove Portions Of This Privacy Policy At Any Time, Without Prior Notice.
QUESTIONS OR COMMENTS
Mtndewds Is Open To Questions And Comments About This Privacy Policy. You Can Reach Our Customer Service Representatives At Support@orage.com Or At 1 (855) 373-0288, Monday To Friday From 9am To 5pm Eastern Time.
@orage89.
